<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Publications on Ke (Kerr) Lyu</title>
    <link>https://KerrLyu.github.io/research/publications/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Publications on Ke (Kerr) Lyu</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2021 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.wangchucheng.com/&#34;&gt;WANG Chucheng&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.ruiqima.com/&#34;&gt;MA Ruiqi&lt;/a&gt;
</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://KerrLyu.github.io/research/publications/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Social Capital and Self-employment Dynamics in China</title>
      <link>https://KerrLyu.github.io/research/publications/2023-social_capital/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 1969 16:33:43 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://KerrLyu.github.io/research/publications/2023-social_capital/</guid>
      <description>Abstract Abstract: Opportunity-driven entrepreneurship could stimulate economic growth and foster technology innovation while subsistence-driven self-employment could have the opposite eﬀect. In China, a country with a typical relational society, and a middle-income status, the nature of nonagricultural self-employment remains contentious. Examining the influence of social capital on entrepreneurial activities could provide insight into the nature of entrepreneurial activities in China, though this issue has received relatively little attention in the literature. To address this gap, this study employs multivariate discrete choice modeling on national representative samples from the China Family Panel Studies dataset to assess the relationship between social capital and entrepreneurship dynamics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Economic and Environmental Effects of Resource Tax Reform in China: A Computable General Equilibrium</title>
      <link>https://KerrLyu.github.io/research/publications/2019-tax/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 1969 16:33:39 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://KerrLyu.github.io/research/publications/2019-tax/</guid>
      <description>Download paper here
Lyu, K., &amp;amp; Sun, J. (2019, December). Economic and Environmental Effects of Resource Tax Reform in China: A Computable General Equilibrium. In 2nd International Symposium on Social Science and Management Innovation (SSMI 2019) (pp. 447-454). Atlantis Press.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reanalysis of Empirical Research for Return to Schooling: a Weak Instrument Variable Problem</title>
      <link>https://KerrLyu.github.io/research/publications/2019-education/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 1969 16:33:39 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://KerrLyu.github.io/research/publications/2019-education/</guid>
      <description>Download paper here
Lyu, K., &amp;amp; Jiang, Z. (2019). Reanalysis of Empirical Research for Return to Schooling: a Weak Instrument Variable Problem. In Proceedings of the 2019 International Seminar on Education, Teaching, Business and Management (ISETBM 2019), Moscow, Russia, November 2-3, 2019. DOI: 10.25236/isetbm.2019.040</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
