<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Teaching on Ke (Kerr) Lyu</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/teaching/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Teaching on Ke (Kerr) Lyu</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/teaching/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Teaching Philosophy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/teaching/teaching-philosophy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/teaching/teaching-philosophy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;teaching-philosophy&#34;&gt;Teaching Philosophy&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As an economics educator, I see teaching as a collaborative process of discovery, where students learn to think critically, solve problems with data, and engage with real-world policy questions. I leverage &lt;strong&gt;technology intentionally&lt;/strong&gt; to enhance this process—transforming lectures into interactive spaces and assignments into hands-on learning experiences.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I regularly integrate digital platforms to foster &lt;strong&gt;active participation&lt;/strong&gt;. Tools like &lt;strong&gt;Mentimeter&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;Top Hat&lt;/strong&gt; allow for real-time polling, anonymous Q&amp;amp;A, and live problem-solving. During lessons on inflation or unemployment, I use these tools to pose questions such as &lt;em&gt;“Which shock shifts the Phillips Curve?”&lt;/em&gt; or &lt;em&gt;“How would you classify today’s labor market?”&lt;/em&gt;—stimulating immediate reflection and peer comparison. These real-time checks help me adjust pacing and ensure that no one falls behind.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teaching with Technology - Mentimeter</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/teaching/tech-example/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/teaching/tech-example/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;teaching-with-technology-real-time-polling-with-mentimeter&#34;&gt;Teaching with Technology: Real-Time Polling with Mentimeter&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In my &lt;em&gt;Principles of Macroeconomics&lt;/em&gt; class, I integrated &lt;strong&gt;Mentimeter&lt;/strong&gt; across the semester to build a more interactive and engaging classroom experience. This three-part approach included a pre-course survey, real-time knowledge checks, and reflection activities through word clouds.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;part-1-pre-class-survey-to-understand-student-preferences&#34;&gt;Part 1: Pre-class Survey to Understand Student Preferences&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Before the course began, I surveyed students on their preferred learning formats and macroeconomic interests. This allowed me to adjust the structure and content of the course to better match their preferences.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
