<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Working Papers on Ke (Kerr) Lyu</title>
    <link>https://KerrLyu.github.io/research/working_paper/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Working Papers on Ke (Kerr) Lyu</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2021 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.wangchucheng.com/&#34;&gt;WANG Chucheng&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.ruiqima.com/&#34;&gt;MA Ruiqi&lt;/a&gt;
</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://KerrLyu.github.io/research/working_paper/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>From Vice to Venture: Evaluating the Impact of Smoking and Drinking on Self-employment in China</title>
      <link>https://KerrLyu.github.io/research/working_paper/2023-smoking/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 1969 16:33:43 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://KerrLyu.github.io/research/working_paper/2023-smoking/</guid>
      <description>Abstract Risky health behaviors, such as smoking and alcohol abuse, not only lead to preventable deaths but also affect workplace performance. Using data from the China Health and Nutrition Survey, this study examines how these behaviors influence the choice between solo self-employment, employer entrepreneurship, and paid employment. The study employs the instrumental variable approach, using cigarette and alcohol prices as instruments. The findings reveal that increased smoking and drinking behaviors reduce the likelihood of choosing self-employment, regardless of its type.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The impact of low-carbon city pilot policy on urban energy transition: an analysis of multiple mediating effects based on “government-enterprise-resident”</title>
      <link>https://KerrLyu.github.io/research/working_paper/2023-did/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 1969 16:33:43 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://KerrLyu.github.io/research/working_paper/2023-did/</guid>
      <description>Abstract The global energy transition is crucial for all nations due to increasing concerns about energy security and climate change. The low-carbon city pilot (LCCP) policy is an essential project in the energy transition process, but its impact on urban energy transition (ET) and the underlying mechanisms remain unclear. To address this, we use a multi-temporal Difference In Difference (DID) model, analyzing panel data from 277 Chinese cities spanning 2006 to 2020, to examine the effects of the LCCP policy on urban energy transition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Towards sustainable development: The spatial spillover effects of low-carbon city pilot policy on urban energy transition</title>
      <link>https://KerrLyu.github.io/research/working_paper/2023-sdid/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 1969 16:33:43 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://KerrLyu.github.io/research/working_paper/2023-sdid/</guid>
      <description>Abstract The Low-Carbon City Pilot (LCCP) policy is a significant project in energy transition which is a critical global task due to concerns about energy security and climate change. However, few studies have focused on the spatial spillover effects and mechanism role of LCCP policy on energy transition. To address this gap, this study employs a sample dataset comprising 277 cities from 2006 to 2020 and adopts Spatial Difference-In-Differences (SDID) model to explore this key spatial spillover effect exhibited by pilot cities.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
