<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ke (Kerr) Lyu</title>
    <link>https://KerrLyu.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Ke (Kerr) Lyu</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://KerrLyu.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Credit Market Auction Game</title>
      <link>https://KerrLyu.github.io/teaching/credit_market_auction/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://KerrLyu.github.io/teaching/credit_market_auction/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This game is designed to help freshmen university students understand the credit market and
game theory by engaging in a competitive auction for loan opportunities. Participants will take on the roles
of lenders, attempting to maximize their returns while considering their competitors&amp;rsquo; strategies.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Job Market Bingo Game</title>
      <link>https://KerrLyu.github.io/teaching/job_market_bingo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://KerrLyu.github.io/teaching/job_market_bingo/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;To help students understand the dynamics of employment and unemployment in the labor market through
a fun, interactive game that involves matching job-related factors with their consequences and discussing
their implications.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Supply and Demand Game</title>
      <link>https://KerrLyu.github.io/teaching/supply_and_demand/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://KerrLyu.github.io/teaching/supply_and_demand/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this game, students will take on the role of buyers and sellers in a market for a particular product. The
goal of the game is to find the equilibrium price and quantity in the market by adjusting their buying and
selling behavior, taking into account their costs and available money.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching Philosophy</title>
      <link>https://KerrLyu.github.io/teaching/teaching-philosophy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://KerrLyu.github.io/teaching/teaching-philosophy/</guid>
      <description>Teaching Philosophy As an economics educator, I employ active learning through assisted knowledge creation—a pedagogical approach refined over three years of teaching courses ranging from Principles of Macroeconomics to Labor Economics. My methods adapt to class dynamics:
Small Classes (15–25 students) Build rapport through weekly 1:1 check-ins to align course goals with career interests (e.g., tailoring regression projects to students&amp;rsquo; policy or industry aspirations) Facilitate Socratic debates on topics like minimum wage impacts, where students role-play as policymakers, union reps, and small business owners Large Lectures (60+ students) Deploy Mentimeter for real-time concept checks (e.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Technology in Teaching</title>
      <link>https://KerrLyu.github.io/teaching/tech-example/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://KerrLyu.github.io/teaching/tech-example/</guid>
      <description>🎓 Teaching with Technology: A Classroom Game Example In my Principles of Macroeconomics course, I integrated live, tech-enhanced simulations to teach complex economic concepts like supply and demand in an engaging and interactive way.
🎯 Objective Make abstract economic concepts tangible by turning the classroom into a live marketplace using collaborative tools and real-time visual feedback.
🛠 Tools Used Google Sheets with live graphs Mobile devices and QR codes GitHub-hosted game interface Projector for real-time visualization 🎮 Activity: Supply and Demand Market Game Students are randomly assigned as buyers or sellers.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
