<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ke (Kerr) Lyu</title>
    <link>https://KerrLyu.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Ke (Kerr) Lyu</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2021 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.wangchucheng.com/&#34;&gt;WANG Chucheng&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.ruiqima.com/&#34;&gt;MA Ruiqi&lt;/a&gt;
</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://KerrLyu.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Credit Market Auction Game</title>
      <link>https://KerrLyu.github.io/teaching/econ_103/credit_market_auction/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://KerrLyu.github.io/teaching/econ_103/credit_market_auction/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This game is designed to help freshmen university students understand the credit market and
game theory by engaging in a competitive auction for loan opportunities. Participants will take on the roles
of lenders, attempting to maximize their returns while considering their competitors&amp;rsquo; strategies.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Job Market Bingo Game</title>
      <link>https://KerrLyu.github.io/teaching/econ_103/job_market_bingo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://KerrLyu.github.io/teaching/econ_103/job_market_bingo/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;To help students understand the dynamics of employment and unemployment in the labor market through
a fun, interactive game that involves matching job-related factors with their consequences and discussing
their implications.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Supply and Demand Game</title>
      <link>https://KerrLyu.github.io/teaching/econ_103/supply_and_demand/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://KerrLyu.github.io/teaching/econ_103/supply_and_demand/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this game, students will take on the role of buyers and sellers in a market for a particular product. The
goal of the game is to find the equilibrium price and quantity in the market by adjusting their buying and
selling behavior, taking into account their costs and available money.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>From Vice to Venture: Evaluating the Impact of Smoking and Drinking on Self-employment in China</title>
      <link>https://KerrLyu.github.io/research/working_paper/2023-smoking/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 1969 16:33:43 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://KerrLyu.github.io/research/working_paper/2023-smoking/</guid>
      <description>Abstract Risky health behaviors, such as smoking and alcohol abuse, not only lead to preventable deaths but also affect workplace performance. Using data from the China Health and Nutrition Survey, this study examines how these behaviors influence the choice between solo self-employment, employer entrepreneurship, and paid employment. The study employs the instrumental variable approach, using cigarette and alcohol prices as instruments. The findings reveal that increased smoking and drinking behaviors reduce the likelihood of choosing self-employment, regardless of its type.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Capital and Self-employment Dynamics in China</title>
      <link>https://KerrLyu.github.io/research/publications/2023-social_capital/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 1969 16:33:43 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://KerrLyu.github.io/research/publications/2023-social_capital/</guid>
      <description>Abstract Abstract: Opportunity-driven entrepreneurship could stimulate economic growth and foster technology innovation while subsistence-driven self-employment could have the opposite eﬀect. In China, a country with a typical relational society, and a middle-income status, the nature of nonagricultural self-employment remains contentious. Examining the influence of social capital on entrepreneurial activities could provide insight into the nature of entrepreneurial activities in China, though this issue has received relatively little attention in the literature. To address this gap, this study employs multivariate discrete choice modeling on national representative samples from the China Family Panel Studies dataset to assess the relationship between social capital and entrepreneurship dynamics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The impact of low-carbon city pilot policy on urban energy transition: an analysis of multiple mediating effects based on “government-enterprise-resident”</title>
      <link>https://KerrLyu.github.io/research/work_in_progress/2023-health_insu/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 1969 16:33:43 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://KerrLyu.github.io/research/work_in_progress/2023-health_insu/</guid>
      <description>Abstract Abstract: The global energy transition is crucial for all nations due to increasing concerns about energy security and climate change. The low-carbon city pilot (LCCP) policy is an essential project in the energy transition process, but its impact on urban energy transition (ET) and the underlying mechanisms remain unclear. To address this, we use a multi-temporal Difference In Difference (DID) model, analyzing panel data from 277 Chinese cities spanning 2006 to 2020, to examine the effects of the LCCP policy on urban energy transition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The impact of low-carbon city pilot policy on urban energy transition: an analysis of multiple mediating effects based on “government-enterprise-resident”</title>
      <link>https://KerrLyu.github.io/research/work_in_progress/2023-job_creation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 1969 16:33:43 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://KerrLyu.github.io/research/work_in_progress/2023-job_creation/</guid>
      <description>Abstract Abstract: The global energy transition is crucial for all nations due to increasing concerns about energy security and climate change. The low-carbon city pilot (LCCP) policy is an essential project in the energy transition process, but its impact on urban energy transition (ET) and the underlying mechanisms remain unclear. To address this, we use a multi-temporal Difference In Difference (DID) model, analyzing panel data from 277 Chinese cities spanning 2006 to 2020, to examine the effects of the LCCP policy on urban energy transition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The impact of low-carbon city pilot policy on urban energy transition: an analysis of multiple mediating effects based on “government-enterprise-resident”</title>
      <link>https://KerrLyu.github.io/research/working_paper/2023-did/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 1969 16:33:43 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://KerrLyu.github.io/research/working_paper/2023-did/</guid>
      <description>Abstract The global energy transition is crucial for all nations due to increasing concerns about energy security and climate change. The low-carbon city pilot (LCCP) policy is an essential project in the energy transition process, but its impact on urban energy transition (ET) and the underlying mechanisms remain unclear. To address this, we use a multi-temporal Difference In Difference (DID) model, analyzing panel data from 277 Chinese cities spanning 2006 to 2020, to examine the effects of the LCCP policy on urban energy transition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Towards sustainable development: The spatial spillover effects of low-carbon city pilot policy on urban energy transition</title>
      <link>https://KerrLyu.github.io/research/working_paper/2023-sdid/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 1969 16:33:43 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://KerrLyu.github.io/research/working_paper/2023-sdid/</guid>
      <description>Abstract The Low-Carbon City Pilot (LCCP) policy is a significant project in energy transition which is a critical global task due to concerns about energy security and climate change. However, few studies have focused on the spatial spillover effects and mechanism role of LCCP policy on energy transition. To address this gap, this study employs a sample dataset comprising 277 cities from 2006 to 2020 and adopts Spatial Difference-In-Differences (SDID) model to explore this key spatial spillover effect exhibited by pilot cities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Economic and Environmental Effects of Resource Tax Reform in China: A Computable General Equilibrium</title>
      <link>https://KerrLyu.github.io/research/publications/2019-tax/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 1969 16:33:39 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://KerrLyu.github.io/research/publications/2019-tax/</guid>
      <description>Download paper here
Lyu, K., &amp;amp; Sun, J. (2019, December). Economic and Environmental Effects of Resource Tax Reform in China: A Computable General Equilibrium. In 2nd International Symposium on Social Science and Management Innovation (SSMI 2019) (pp. 447-454). Atlantis Press.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reanalysis of Empirical Research for Return to Schooling: a Weak Instrument Variable Problem</title>
      <link>https://KerrLyu.github.io/research/publications/2019-education/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 1969 16:33:39 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://KerrLyu.github.io/research/publications/2019-education/</guid>
      <description>Download paper here
Lyu, K., &amp;amp; Jiang, Z. (2019). Reanalysis of Empirical Research for Return to Schooling: a Weak Instrument Variable Problem. In Proceedings of the 2019 International Seminar on Education, Teaching, Business and Management (ISETBM 2019), Moscow, Russia, November 2-3, 2019. DOI: 10.25236/isetbm.2019.040</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
